when inkscape released version 1.0
Inkscape发布1.0版时
earlier this year they made a pretty big
今年早些时候，他们做了一次相当大的
change to the way that the stroke to
更改为笔划的方式
path function works
路径函数起作用
and it was significant enough that it
它的重要性足以让它
actually broke some of my older
实际上弄坏了我的一些较老的
tutorials
教程
so i wanted to put this video together
所以我想把这段视频放在一起
to address this problem and how you can
要解决此问题，以及如何
work around it if you're following along
如果你正在跟随它，那就绕过它
with one of my older tutorials
用我以前的一本教程
and getting stuck on the stroke to path
在划水的路上被卡住了
part
零件
[Music]
[音乐]
so on my screen here i have two
所以在我的屏幕上我有两个
different versions of inkscape opened
打开了不同版本的Inkscape
this is the older version of inkscape
这是较旧版本的Inkscape
which is
这就是
0.92.5 and then this over here is the
0.92.5然后这里是
new version of inkscape which is version
Inkscape的新版本是
1.0
1.0
and as you can see i have the same
如你所见，我也有同样的
object posted into each
对象发布到每个
each installation if you notice this is
如果您注意到，每个安装都是
a circle it's a green circle with a
一个圆圈是一个绿色的圆圈，上面有一个
green fill and a red stroke as you can
尽可能地用绿色填充和红色描边
see here in the data
请看这里的数据
the fill is green the stroke is red and
填充是绿色的，笔触是红色的
what happens is
发生的事情是
in the older version of inkscape if you
在旧版本的Inkscape中，如果您
go to path
转到路径
stroke to path it takes that red stroke
笔划到小路，那红色的笔划
and turns it into a path of its own if
并将其变成一条自己的道路，如果
you go to the nodes tool you'll see
转到结点工具，您将看到
now that is now a red object of its own
现在它本身就是一个红色物体了
it's no longer a stroke
它不再是中风
so let me just undo that and come over
所以让我把它解开，然后过来
here to the newer version of inkscape to
从这里到较新版本的Inkscape
show you how it works now
现在向您展示它是如何工作的
now if you go to path stroke to path
现在，如果您转到路径笔划到路径
nothing visual nothing visibly changes
没有什么视觉上的，没有任何明显的改变
on the screen but what it did was it
在屏幕上，但它所做的是
took
拿
this it took the red stroke and turned
就这样，它闯了红灯，转身
it into a path of its own
它走上了一条自己的道路
only it didn't get rid of the green fill
只是它没有去掉绿色填充物
it kept the green fill as a separate
它将绿色填充物作为一个单独的
object
对象
grouped together with the red stroke and
与红色笔触组合在一起，
to see what i mean you'll have to go to
要明白我的意思，你必须去
object
对象
ungroup and you can see it is now two
解组后，您可以看到现在是两个
separate objects so you have this here
将物体分开，这样你就有了这个
you have this red stroke which is now
你有这个红色的笔划，现在是
its own path but it also
它自己的道路，但它也
kept this green fill here as a separate
将这个绿色填充物作为一个单独的
object
对象
so let me undo this even further i want
所以让我更进一步地撤销我想要的
to show you what the uh the work around
向你展示一下，呃，周围的工作
is now
现
let's come back over here to the
让我们回到这里，回到
original one now in the if you're
原版现已在《如果你是
following along with one of these
接下来是其中的一个
tutorials and i tell you to do stroke to
教程和我告诉你做划水
path
路径
break apart union let me show you how
拆散联盟，让我教你怎么做
that works if you go to path
如果您转到PATH，这将起作用
stroke to path path break apart
笔划到路径路径断开
path union you end up with this right
路径并集你最终得到了这个权利
here
这里
this this sequence doesn't work in the
这个序列不能在
new installation of inkscape though so
Inkscape的新安装虽然如此
what you have to do is you have to
你要做的是你必须
select it
选择它
and go to path stroke to path
并转到路径笔划到路径
and then object on group
然后是组上的对象
and then path union so basically what
然后是路径联盟，所以基本上是什么
you're doing is we're taking the
你所做的就是我们要把
sequence
序列
stroke to path break apart union and
笔划到路径拆分并和
replacing it with
将其替换为
stroke to path on group union i'll have
在团体联盟上划出一条路我会有
this all written
这都是写好的
out in the description below in case you
在下面的描述中删除，以防您
find it easier to follow along with that
发现跟上这一步更容易
so
所以
i just wanted to put this video together
我只是想把这段视频拼凑在一起
real quick to address that problem
很快就能解决这个问题
hopefully this isn't too much of a
希望这不会是太大的
disruption to your learning experience
中断您的学习体验
if you have any questions just leave a
如果您有任何问题，请在
comment below and as always thanks for
在下面发表评论，并一如既往地感谢
watching
观看
[Music]
[音乐]